Santiago Otálvaro Ospina

Middle backend developer | Java Developer | .Net Developer | Systems engineer

Profile Summary

Experienced working on teams focused in FullStack development. Skilled in Java, C#, Spring Boot and .NET. Good knowledge of design patterns, good programming practices and SOLID principles. Development of some personal applications using different technologies.

Work Experience

SERACIS LTDA

Professional practices Dec.. 2021 - Jun. 2022

Frontend and backend developer, building an application of the PAE "School Feeding Program" for the management of students of the "Normal Superior de Envigado" school.

SERACIS LTDA

Backend Developer Jun. 2021 - Dec. 2021

Frontend and backend developer, building and maintaining web applications using Spring boot, .NET Framework and .NET 5

Telemed Soluciones BPO SAS

Software Developer Apr. 2020 - Feb. 2021

Creation of virtual agent for massive inbound or outbound campaigns and reporting in power BI real time reports.

Education

Universidad de Antioquia

Systems engineer Feb. 2016 - Sep. 2022

Colegio Parroquial San Buenaventura

High school degree Dic. 2015

Certifications

Udemy

Java Programming Masterclass covering Java 11 Nov 2018

Language

Spanish: Native English: B2

Technical Skill

- Design patterns
- Architectural patterns
- Relational database
- · SOLID principles

Languages and Frameworks

Java C# JavaScript Spring Boot .Net Angular

Employee referral

employee referral are provided upon request

Contact



+57 305 3036942



Sotalvaroo1999@gmail.com



Linkedin.com/in/sotalvaroo



repository https://github.com/SotalvaroO